Anggriawan Rayzadmiko

Bogor Regency, West Java | +6281310008091 | anggriawan.net@gmail.com | https://linkedin.com/in/anggriawanr | https://razd-net.vercel.app

Summary

A fresh graduate in System and Instrumentation Physics, who has a great interest in Web Development and Software Engineering. Thanks to hard work, I managed to get a cum laude predicate with a GPA of 3.51. I myself am a fast learner who is self-taught, interested in learning new technologies, and can work in teams or individually. Currently I have learned a lot of new technologies over the past year and have 1 year of experience designing UI and managing social media in the Exedu Start-up Project, creating up-to-date UI designs for the web using Figma.

Experience

Erlangga Dec 2022 – Aug 2023

Freelance – Video Editor & Korektor

- Created animation video using Adobe After Effects
- Created assets for the animation
- · Responsible for video quality according to client requests
- Created digital books with Adobe InDesign, up to 144+ books
- Initiate discussion with story writer to ensure validity of video material

BRIN Aug 2022 – Nov 2022

Research Assistant

- Modeled and developed a PID controller using Raspberry Pi programmed with Python and tuning it, achieve a very stable response on rocket flight
- Modeled and developed a control system for rocket VTOL that achive miss distance less than
 1 meter on simulation
- Suggested the controller algorithm method
- Assisted in a journal writing

Exedu Start-Up Project

Jul 2021 – Jul 2022

UI Designer

- Designed a google based website (Google Sites) that have more than 1500 users
- Created a website prototype in Figma and collaborated with Product Manager
- Collaborated with content writer to maximize the UI design according to the content, achieve a responsive web across any platform
- Designed attractive content design to reach the public in instagram

Universitas Indonesia Feb – Jul 2022

Control System Laboratory Assistant

- Evaluated practitioner's competence in the form of a presentation
- Trained practitioners about control theory in practice with microcontroller and data acquisition software

Lembaga Penerbangan dan Antariksa Negara (LAPAN)

Jul – Sept 2021

Graduated: Jul 2022

Research Intern

- Built a PID controller with LabVIEW and implement it on rocket flight guidance and VTOL, resulting miss distance less than 1 meter on simulation
- Reported the progress and method of the controller algorithm

Education

Universitas Indonesia

Bachelor of Science – Physics – Instrumentation Physics

GPA 3.51/4.00 - Cum Laude

- Thesis Research: Design of Cold Probe Temperature Controller on Thermoelectric Material Characterization System using Microcontroller
- Digital Signal Processing Project: Speech Recognition Based on Mel Spectrogram with Deep Learning using MATLAB and Python
- Sensors and Actuators Project: Design and Build Vehicle Noise Test System for Two-Wheel Motor Vehicle

Technical Skills

- JavaScript
- HTML5/CSS3
- ReactJS
- NodeJS/ExpressJS
- Git
- NextJS
- UI/UX
- MongoDB
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Figma
- Prisma ORM

Organization and Volunteer

Physics Department Student Association

Staff Feb 2020 - Feb 2021

Designed attractive content to reach the public in instagram and students

Pesta Rakyat Fisika (PRF)

Staff of Quiz Competition at Elementary School Level
Designed attractive and interactive question with PowerPoint

Jan - Februari 2020

Projects

Blogin

A blog web project that allows users to create a blog with markdown that can be seen by everyone. The project can be visited in this link: https://blogin-razd.vercel.app

Razd-net

A portfolio website to show off my front-end skills. The project can be visited in this link https://razd-net.vercel.app

Certificate

• NodeJS: Pemula sampai Mahir

Udemy, 2024

• Belajar Dasar Pemrograman JavaScript

Dicoding, 2023

• Belajar Membuat Front-End Web untuk Pemula

Dicoding, 2023

Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Web dengan React

Dicoding, 2023

Python Essentials 1

Cisco, 2022

• Python Essentials 2

Cisco, 2022